翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Now that we understand the intricacies that go into solving the mystery of the walrus,
我们已经破解了海象之谜的复杂之处
we're ready to finally build a list.
是时候构建一个 List 了
So the difference between a list and an array is that a list is going to be able to grow arbitrarily large,
List 和数组的不同之处在于 List 可以随意变大
unlike a Java array, which is of a fixed size.
而 Java 数组的大小是固定的
So we're going to build this totally from scratch.
我们从头做起
And for reasons that won't be clear right now,
出自于暂时未知的原因
our list is going to have two variables.
我们的 List 将有两个变量
The first is going to be an integer called first and the second will be a pointer, or an address of, another int list.
第一个是整型 first，第二个是指针或称为地址，指向 IntList
And our list ultimately is going to be used for storing only integers for simplicity.
为简单起见，我们的 List 最终将仅用于存储整型
So let's start off this class.
让我们开始吧
So our class is called IntList, and as promised,
我们的类叫 IntList
we're going to have public int first and then public IntList rest.
首先写 public int first，然后是 public IntList rest
Now if you came from 61A, you roughly know where this is going.
如果你来自61A，大概知道这是怎么回事
Otherwise, it may be a little mysterious.
否则它可能会有点神秘
So it turns out that we've actually already implemented a list.
事实上我们已经实现了一个 List
We're done.
结束了
What?
什么？
How can that be?
这怎么可能呢？
Well let's try it out.
那我们试试吧
I'm going to make an IntList called L. OK?
我要创建一个名为 L 的 IntList
So IntList L, we can say new IntList,
所以 IntList L = new IntList()
and then we could say L.first equals 5, L.rest equals null,
然后 L.first = 5，L.rest = null
and that would be a list that contains the number 5.
这是一个包含数字5的 List
I could then say--
然后...
actually, you know what?
你知道吗？
No. I think L.rest is going to be a new IntList and then L.rest.first is going to be 10.
L.rest 将创建新的 IntList，且 first 变量设为10
And so forth.
以此类推
Now this is a little awkward, of course, to use but let's keep going.
这个看起来有点笨拙，但继续吧
So we could say L.rest.rest equals new IntList.
还可以写 L.rest.rest = new IntList()
L.rest.rest.first equals 15.
L.rest.rest.first = 15
And at this point, we--
这时候我们...
well, can't really see what's going on.
看不出发生了什么
So I'm going to Take this code and I'm going to copy it into our good old Java Visualizer so we can understand what's going on.
所以我将这段代码复制到 Java visualizer 中，了解发生了什么
So if we visualize the execution of this class,
可视化这个类
after I create this first list--
创建了第一个 List 后
scroll forward.
向前滚动
After these three lines of code are done,
完成这三行代码之后
I have L in IntList which has a value called first 5 and rest null.
有了一个 IntList 类型的变量 L，它的 first 为5，rest 为 null
So if I run these next two lines of code,
运行接下来的两行代码
which I'll skim forward to-- so these two lines of code are done.
快速浏览一下，这两行代码已经完成了
L.rest is now a new IntList, which has first 10 and rest null.
rest 现在指向新的 IntList，first 为10，rest 为 null
Well at this point, if we tried to imagine,
这时我们可以想想
how would I add a third value to the list?
如何将第三个值添加到 List 中？
We could say L.rest.rest, and in that case, we'd be talking about this box right here.
可以写 L.rest.rest，这样我们讨论的是这个盒子
L.rest.rest equals new IntList.
L.rest.rest = new IntList()
So after I say L.rest.rest equals new IntList,
所以执行 L.rest.rest = new IntList() 后
what do you suppose happens?
你认为会发生什么？
OK, so I'll just skim forward a little bit.
稍微向前看一下
We end up getting an IntList which has the default values of all zeros.
我们最终得到一个 IntList，它的默认值为全零
And at that point, we could say, OK, you know what?
这时我们可以让
L.rest.rest.first is 15.
L.rest.rest.first = 15
In that case, we are telling Java that we'd like to set this box--
在这种情况下，我们告诉 Java 想要设置这个盒子
this memory box here-- its bits equal to 15.
这个盒子的内存的比特等于15
So what we've done now is build the list.
现在我们建立了 List
Now of course it's a little awkward to use, right?
用起来有点笨拙是吧？
I mean, like, who wants to write code that looks like this?
谁愿意写出这样的代码呢？
So we can make things slightly better by working a little bit backwards.
所以稍微倒退一点优化它
So first, I'm going to create a constructor where I'm going to say public IntList int, f, IntList, r.
先创建一个构造函数，public IntList(int f, IntList r)
And then I'm going to say f equals first, rest equals r.
f = first，rest = r
And then what I'm going to do is I'm actually going to build my list the other way around.
然后使用另一种方式建立 List
So let's try that out.
让我们试试吧
IntList L equals new IntList.
IntList L = new IntList()
I'm going to say 15 null.
参数是15和 null
And then I'm going to say L equals new IntList 10 L.
然后 L = new IntList(10, L)
And then I'm going to say L equals new IntList 5 L.
然后 L = new IntList(5, L)
So this is also kind of awkward code but it's a little more concise.
这种代码也很笨，但稍微简洁一些
So let's try running this and seeing what happens.
试着运行一下，看看会发生什么
OK, any syntax errors?
有语法错误吗？
Nope. Good.
没有，好的
OK, so we say IntList L equals new IntList.
执行 IntList L = new IntList()
That's saying I want a new IntList that has 15 at the front, or as the first value,
这创建了一个新的 IntList，前面的15是 first 的值
and nothing is the rest.
null 是 rest 的值
So after running that, I end up with this.
运行后得到了这个
Now I'm going to say, you know what?
你知道吗？
Actually, you know what I want L to be?
你知道我想让 L 成为什么吗？
I want L to be a list which has 10 at the front and has my old list at the back.
我希望前面是10，后面是旧的 List
So in other words, it should be 10 here and then this list after 10.
这里应该是10，后面是这个 List
So after running this code, sure enough, we get this, right?
运行这段代码之后，我们果然得到了这个
So L is no longer its original list.
L 不再指向原始列表
It is now the new list we just built,
而是指向刚创建的新 List
which has 10 at the front, pointing at this one.
值为10的指向这个
Now when I say L equals new IntList 5 L--
执行 L = new IntList(5, L) 时
and if you're not quite following,
如果你不太明白
I urge you to pause the video and try and read ahead and guess what I'm about to do.
我强烈要求你暂停视频，猜猜我接下来要做什么
So what I'm saying is I want L not to be what it currently is.
我想改变 L 的样子
I want it to be the address of a new list
让它成为新 List 的地址
which has 5 at the front and which points out the old list that I've created.
值为5的在前面，指向旧 List
So in this case, we create a new node.
在本例中，我们创建一个新节点
So here's the new list that we're going to point L at.
这是 L 要指向的新 List
We put the value 5 in.
值设为5
And then you say, you know what?
然后呢？
I want rest to be equal to r.
我希望 rest = r
What's r?
r 是什么？
r is just going to be the address that was passed in in the constructor, which is the old list.
r 是传入构造函数的地址，也就是旧 List
So at that point, rest points at this IntList instance here-- right here, the old list.
这时 rest 指向这里的 IntList 实例，也就是旧 List
And so once everything is said and done,
一切都说完了
we end up with the list 5, 10, 15.
最终得到了 List 5、10、15
So there was nothing new there we haven't seen in the mystery of the walrus,
没什么海象之谜外的新东西
though it can be a little bit hard to wrap your brain around.
尽管这可能让你大脑有些糊涂
And if you didn't quite get it, watch again and try and guess what I'm about to do.
如果你不太明白，再看一遍，试着猜猜我要做什么
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）